<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Angus Harrow Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://angusharrow.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Angus Harrow Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:11:37 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://angusharrow.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Primary School</title>
      <link>https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/primary-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:11:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/primary-school/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The aim of the project is to separate staff and student circulation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The brief needed a primary school in Birkenhead, Merseyside capable of catering for six school years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/primary-school-sketch.png&#34; alt=&#34;Sketch&#34; title=&#34;Sketch&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main challenge was fitting the accommodation schedule on such a small site of 198 sq.m. The design approach was to create a mountain where the classrooms and additional accommodation was staggered around a central hall space. Access for students and parents would be externally through a terrace with staff entering through the main building itself. Inspiration stemmed from memories of my own primary school where, for safety and convenience reasons, children would enter directly from the playground into their classrooms and staff through a separate circulation system.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/primary-school-section.png&#34; alt=&#34;Section&#34; title=&#34;Section&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film School</title>
      <link>https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/film-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 14:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/film-school/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The aim of my project is to create a film hub on campus that links the south west side with current and future hotspots across the university.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It will be a mixed-use sustainable building that provides private and well thought out spaces for film teaching and development whilst also hosting public meeting areas and events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The design is based around the relationship between the studio and cinema boxes. The workshops, control rooms and teaching spaces serve the studio space and there is a visual awareness between the production (studio) and viewing (cinema)&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/film-school-section.png&#34; alt=&#34;Section&#34; title=&#34;Section&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-living Residential Project</title>
      <link>https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/coliving-residential/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:18:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/coliving-residential/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The aim of the project is to create a mixed use building with clear boundaries between private and public spaces. The accommodation needed to house at least twenty residents including two accessible rooms. Other requirements included co-working, social, and recreation spaces. The residents I chose to cater for were young NHS workers stationed at the Royal and Women’s Hospitals in Liverpool.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://angusharrow.github.io/posts/coliving-environmental-section.png&#34; alt=&#34;Environmental Section&#34; title=&#34;Environmental Section&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Public spaces include a gym and cafe with a social plaza that interacts with the street on the south of the site. Private spaces established with the tower act as a threshold between the plaza and atrium. The design used the brick tower for co-working spaces that has access to views of Liverpool’s skyline. The atrium space on the ground and first floors acts as private social and dining spaces. For affordable living, the main accommodation is spread over the second floor in modular living pods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
